http://www.oceanelements.com/privacy-policy

Call 020 3949 8363Live ChatSend EnquiryNewsletter SignupMy Holiday / Manage my HolidayPlease use your 'My Holiday' to check your holiday details, pay balances and book extras.Manage My HolidayEnter your details to retrieve your booking.Login To My AccountThe login details you have provided are incorrect. Please try again.BackBeach
Beach Club Holidays Home
Resorts
Accommodation
Beach Deals
Activities
Family & Groups
Water Sports & Yacht Tuition
Beach Information
Children
> Sea Urchins (4-7yr)
> Sea Tigers (8-13yr)
> RYA Youth Squad (8-13yr)
> Teen Clubs (13+)
Yacht
> All our Yacht Courses
> Start Yachting
> Competent Crew
> Day Skipper
> Beginner Skipper 'Fast-track'
> Flotilla Prep course
Family Beach Holidays
Sea Urchins (4-7)
Sea Tigers (8-13)
Youth Squad (8-13)
Group Beach Holidays
FREE Kids Clubs
FAQs
New to Watersports
Insurance
Kit List
About Us
Be in Your Element
General Terms& Conditions
Get in ContactCustomer LoginEmail SignupBrochure RequestAbout UsFAQDo you need help arranging your holiday?Call one of our experts on 02039498363Make An EnquiryComplete our online formRequest BrochureNewsletter SignupCustomer LoginBeach
Beach Club Holidays Home
Resorts
Accommodation
Beach Deals
Activities
Family & Groups
Water Sports & Yacht Tuition
Beach Information
Children
> Sea Urchins (4-7yr)
> Sea Tigers (8-13yr)
> RYA Youth Squad (8-13yr)
> Teen Clubs (13+)
Yacht
> All our Yacht Courses
> Start Yachting
> Competent Crew
> Day Skipper
> Beginner Skipper 'Fast-track'
> Flotilla Prep course
Family Beach Holidays
Sea Urchins (4-7)
Sea Tigers (8-13)
Youth Squad (8-13)
Group Beach Holidays
FREE Kids Clubs
FAQs
New to Watersports
Insurance
Kit List
About Us
Be in Your Element
General Terms& Conditions
Help & Book020 3949 8363HomePrivacy PolicyiGOSKI Ltd Privacy Policy will extend to include companies and brands: Alpine Elements, iGOSKI, Ocean Elements, Venture Holidays, Venture Vacances and Hotel Hermine Blanche.
Your information:
We are committed to protecting the personal information that you give to us and informing you of how we use the information that we collect from you, and of course obtaining your consent to our disclosure of your information.
Your information” refers to details such as your name, contact details, travel preferences and special needs/disabilities/dietary requirements that you supply us or is supplied to us, including any information about other persons on your booking relating to the same.
Your information is collected when you request information from us, or you contact us and/or if we contact you, or if you ask for a holiday quotation or complete a booking with us. You are responsible for ensuring that other members of your party are aware of the content in this Privacy Policy, and that they consent to your acting on their behalf in all your dealings with us.
We will update your information whenever we get the opportunity to keep it current, complete, accurate and up to date
How we use Your Information.
1.    In order to enable us to provide our holidays, then for services such as booking of accommodation, flights, ski or resort extras, insurance etc., we may disclose your information to our third party providers (UK and overseas). To enable you to travel overseas, it may also be mandatory (as requested govt authorities) to disclose your information for immigration, security or any other reasons which they deem appropriate. Even if not mandatory, we might need to use your information to assist where appropriate, and we will do this at our discretion.
2.    We may have to disclose your information to our “group companies” (including overseas companies) in order to ensure efficient and accurate processing of your booking. We may also disclose your information to our data processing companies, or companies providing our travel and reservation software and systems. Other companies will include customer care companies, business management, re-organisation/structuring and /or for sale of our business (or our group companies), risk assessment, security and crime prevention/detection, research and analysis, marketing, monitoring, measuring and assessing customer purchasing preferences and trends, dispute resolution, credit checking and debt collection.
3.    We may have to supply your information to the Police or any other regulatory body if we are asked to do so, or if we choose to do so. We may disclose your information if it relates to any suspected misuse by you of our web site or any of our web site services.
4.    Aspects of your information (for example health) may be considered “sensitive” or “personal” under the Data Protection Act 1998. We collect this information in order to  cater for your needs We will only accept such “personal information” on condition we have your positive consent. When booking a holiday with us you also agree for your insurers, agents and medical staff, to disclose relevant information (which may be sensitive personal information) to use in instances where we may need to act in the interests of a larger group. By way of example, this may be ensuring any contagion does not spread in the event of an illness which you or another person contracts.
5.    We will endeavour to prevent unauthorised disclosures of your personal information by other people, but we cannot be responsible for any unauthorised disclosures or other breaches of security, or indeed for the actions of others if the information was passed to them with your authority or with the authority of anybody other than us or our associated companies/organisations.
6.    We may transfer, sell or assign any of your information to third parties as a result of a sale, merger, consolidation, change of control, transfer of assets or reorganisation of our business. And this we do in the interests of your holiday experience and our continued product support.
Please note: Outside of the EEA, (European Economic Area), controls on privacy may not be as strong or robust as they are in the UK
If you do not agree to the above then we will not be able to do any form of business with you or indeed to process your booking.
Marketing - Direct
1.    We may send you e-newsletters and posted literature from our group of companies. These may be offers, product updates and resort news/goings on. You will have every opportunity to opt out of such correspondence but our website and reservation staff will otherwise assume you agree to recieving such correspondence when you make a holiday reservation with us. Each E-newsletter we send will give you the option to cancel any further marketing correspondence.
Your Rights
1.   You have the right to ask us for a copy of the information we hold about you by writing to us at admin@alpineelements.co.uk. However we may charge a fee for this service.
2.   You also have the right to ask us to correct any inaccuracies in your information.
3.   You also have the right to request that we do not send you any further marketing information, by writing to us at admin@alpineelements.co.uk. You can opt out of all e-newsletter communication by using he safe unsubscribe button at the bottom of the email.
4.   If you want to view a complete  list of our group companies and brands, please write to admin@alpineelements.co.uk.
How we use Cookies
Cookies help to speed up the booking process so that you do not need to re-type the same information over again. If you are making a purchase we will use cookies to keep track of the transaction from one page to the next. We do not store any personal information in the cookie
We also use cookies to collect information relating to customer use and patterns. We use cookies and software tools to capture, measure and analyse site usage and related information.
When you are on our website, we use cookies to provide you with a more personal experience. In other words we use it to do things like remember what you've searched for (rather than typing it again when a new page loads) and to remember saved/recently searched accommodation
Our website or associated website(s) may link through to supplier or third party websites. We are not in control or responsible for their privacy policy and so we would ask that you avail yourself of their terms if required.
If you wish to restrict or block the cookies which are set by our website, or indeed any other website, you can do this through your browser settings (please be aware that restricting cookies may impact on the functionality of our website):
Cookies: Frequently Asked Questions - https://www.aboutcookies.org/cookie-faq/
How to control cookies - https://www.aboutcookies.org/how-to-control-cookies/
How to delete cookies - https://www.aboutcookies.org/how-to-delete-cookies/
Cookies for Advertising
When you are on the web but not necessarily on our website, then in order to help us deliver targetted advertising and avoid repeating advertisments, we work with carefully select 3rd parties whom we allow to employ cookies on our site, on our behalf. These cookies enable us to deliver adverts on other websites that are relevant to a user's interests. The information that we collect and share is anonymous and not personally identifiable. It does not contain a user's name, address, telephone number or email address.
Some of our Cookies:
Criteo: Criteo show personalised adverts when you are browsing other websites based on the holidays that you've viewed on our website. Thedata  collected by these cookies is anonymous. To opt out of receiving these cookies please visit www.criteo.com/en/privacy-policy/opt-out.
Rocket Fuel: These cookies allow us to monitor and enhance the performance of paid-for marketing activity via selected third parties. All information collected is anonymous. For more information please visit: http://rocketfuel.com/privacy-policy
Yahoo: These cookies enable us to collect anonymous, aggregated visitor information including the number of visits and page views that arise from marketing activity. The data stored in these cookies is only used internally.
Response Tap: These cookies allowus to track the interaction between our website and sales centre to help us improve customer experience. The data collected is anonymous and only used internally.
If you have any further questions about our use of cookies please email us on info@alpineelements.co.uk
Monitoring
To help us to improve our service and to ensure mistakes are not made in carrying out your instructions, and in the interests of security, we may monitor and record your telephone calls and your transactions and activities carried out on our website. All recordings will remain the sole property of us. We may also record you via CCTV at our premises (both UK and overseas).
Security Statement & Changes
We have taken and will take all reasonable steps to protect your information. If we make any changes to this Policy, then they will be posted on our website or made available on request.About Us
Contact Us
Terms & Conditions
Privacy Policy
Email Signup
Brochure Request
FAQ
Press OfficeFollow UsEmail newsletter signupSign upThis site uses cookies.We use cookies to ensure you get the best experience on our Website.Cookie and Privacy Policy informationAccept Cookies
